mediasharesuite.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy - Media Share Suite | Online Video, Audio & Photo Sharing Script

**Privacy Statement for MediaShareSuite.com**  
MediaShareSuite.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: MediaShareSuite.com

**Personal Information**  
Any information we collect, including your e-mail and mailing address, are not shared with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes except where explicitly implied.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. MediaShareSuite.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums and FAQ**  
This site makes forums, message boards, and FAQ groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal or server information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. No one can view your account information without your password, which you can change anytime you want.

**Credit Card information is not an issue as MediaShareSuite.com uses a third party service for secure credit card transactions .**

**Contacting the website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can Contact us.
